Peter Wexler papers 1965 - ongoing
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Papers., Series:I
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - Between the Wars. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - 1900 to WWI. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - Spanish American War. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - Civil War. Transparency. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - Japan 1854. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - China 1842. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - Siam 1833. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - War of 1812. Perry. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - J.P. Jones. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - Transition. Transparency. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - At Their Ease. Transparency. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - Doing Their Job. Transparency. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - After Burner. Transparency. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - Men and Women. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. Research. - The Job. Transparency. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Test Slide. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Research. Transition. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Media Research Memo. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Misc. Storyboard Sequences. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Storyboards. As Submitted 3/5/87. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Original Storyboard Blanks. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Original Storyboard Art. Assorted. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Storyboards. Inter. Ver. 3. 1987 (Box 46)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Storyboards. Final 6/17/87. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Preliminary Visual Menu. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Report. Costume Design. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Film Notes. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Detail Pag. Light. Aud. Proj. Des. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Final Pryrotech Design. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Lighting Design. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Preliminary Pageant Set Design. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Detail Pageant Set Design. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Visual Reproductions Lot 1. Phase 1. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - A/V Report Historical. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - A/V Report Current Lot 1. Phase 1. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Preliminary Script. Integ. Scenario. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Preliminary Script. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Detail Script. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Final Script with Cues. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Preliminary Audio Menu. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Audio Menu. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Preliminary Score Menu. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Final Score Menu. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Final Score Arrangement. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Music Rights. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Pre-Set and Safety List. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Manual by Theatre Technology. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Photos of Completed Facility. slides. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Summary Chart. Sheet Description. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Program Copy and Layout. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Making of Navy '87. slides. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Contracting. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Memorandum. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Transmittals. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Business. Early Contract Forms. 3 of 3. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy Summer Pageant. - Business. Contract. 1 of 3. 1987 (Box 47)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. 1986-1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. - Business. Subcontractors. 2 of 3. 1986-1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. - Proposal. Contracting. 1986-1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. - Memorandums. 1987 to 1988. 1986-1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. - Contact List. 1986-1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. - Proposal. Research Photos. 2. 1986-1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Pageant. - Proposal. Study. 1986. 1986-1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Bows. Negatives. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - American Flag. Negatives and transparency. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Semaphore Flag. empty. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Signal Flag. empty. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Navy Flags. empty. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Navy on Watch. Negatives and transparency. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Homecoming. Negatives and transparency. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Current Events. Negatives, photos, slides. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - The People. Negatives and transparency. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - At Sea. Negatives and transparency. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Embark. Negatives. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Training. empty. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Flag Raising. Negatives. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Vietnam. Negatives. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Korea into 1960s. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - VSS Missouri. empty. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Pearl Harbor and WWII. Negatives. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Time Between Wars. empty. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - WWI Byrd. empty. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - 1900 to WWI. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Spanish American War. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Navy in 1800s. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - War of 1812. empty. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Revolutionary. negatives. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Transition. negatives. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - At Their Ease. empty. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Doing Her Job. empty. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Age Rank and Race. Negatives. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Job, Boss, XO, CO. Negatives. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - After Burner. Negatives. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. Research. - Transition. Negatives. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Photo Releases. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Slide Blanks. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Storyboard Blanks. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Storyboard Origninal Art. Polaroids. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Storyboard as Opening. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Storyboard as Submitted. 1989. (Box 48)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Music. 3 files. 1989. (Box 49)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Lighting. Show floppy disk. 1989. (Box 49)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Deliverables. Task 2. 1989. (Box 49)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Deliverables. Task 1. 1989. (Box 49)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Scores. 1989. (Box 49)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Research. 1989. (Box 49)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Script as of Opening. 1989. (Box 49)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Script as Submitted. 1989. (Box 49)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Summary Charts and Sheets. 1989. (Box 49)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Calendar. 1989. (Box 49)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Press and Public Relations. 1989. (Box 49)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Business. 1989. (Box 49)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Memorandums. 1989. (Box 49)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Contact Lists. 1989. (Box 49)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Transmittals. 1989. (Box 49)
  - Navy. Summer Ceremony. - Half Frame Masks. Envelope. Container. 1989. (Box 49)
  - Search for Life. Tour. (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour. - Video Boxes and Labels. 1988 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour. - Washington Hotels. 1988 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour. - Current Tour. (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour. - Current Tour. - Contact Sheets. 1988 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour. - Current Tour. - General Transmittals. 1988 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour. - Current Tour. - General Memorandum. 2 files. 1988 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour. - Current Tour. - Phone Notes. 1990 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour. - Current Tour. - Business. 2 files. 1990 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour. - Current Tour. - Project Budget Tracking. 1988 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour. - Current Tour. - Possible Venues. Correspondence. 1989 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour. - Current Tour. - Possible Venues. Bell Museum, MN. 2 files. 1989 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour. - Current Tour. - Possible Venues. Maryland Scientific Center. 1989 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour. - Current Tour. - Possible Venues. NJ Agricultural Museum. 1989 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour. - Current Tour. - Possible Venues. Trammel Crow Company. 1989 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour. - Current Tour. - Possible Venues. Trammel Crow Center, Dallas. 1989 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour. - Current Tour. - Estimated Costs. 1989 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour. - Current Tour. - Grant Proposals. 1989 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour. - Current Tour. - Suggested Allocation of Grant Monies. 1989 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour Cold Spring Harbor. 1987-1988 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour Cold Spring Harbor. - Transmittals. 1987 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour Cold Spring Harbor. - Memorandum. 2 files. 1987 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour Cold Spring Harbor. - Budget. 1987 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour Cold Spring Harbor. - Contracts. 1987 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour Cold Spring Harbor. - Press and Public Relations. 1987 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour Cold Spring Harbor. - Items Charts. Tour. 1988 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour Cold Spring Harbor. - Computer Floppies. 1988 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour Cold Spring Harbor. - Additional Labels. 1988 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour Cold Spring Harbor. - Text. Voice Over. 1988 (Box 50)
  - Search for Life. Tour Cold Spring Harbor. - Background. 1988 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. Tour Cold Spring Harbor. - USDA Media. 1988 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. 1986-1989 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - Transmittals. 1987 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - Memorandum. 1987 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - Memorandum. 1986 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - Business. 1989 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - Research Memorandum. 1986 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - Show Budget Tracking. 1987 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - Business. 1987 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - Budget and Contract. Variety. 1987 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - Budget and Contract. Theatre Tech. 1987 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - Press and Public Relations. 1987 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - March 2, 1987 Gala. 1986 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - Catalogues. 1986 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - Poster. 1987 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - Exhibitable Materials Package. 1986 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - Computer Floppies. 1987 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - AVI Slide Production. 1987 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - Video Production. 1987 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - Variety Maintenance Manual. 1987 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - Maintenance. Six Months. Show. 1986 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - Crowd Control Reports. 1986 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - Schedules and Contact Lists. 1986 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. University of Maryland. Smithsonian. - USDA Meeting and Phone Log. 1987 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. Filmore Bender Final Report to Kellogg. 1986 (Box 51)
  - Search for Life. Scripting. Scripts. 1987 (Box 52)
  - Search for Life. Scripting. Scripts. - Final Paperwork Package. 1987 (Box 52)
  - Search for Life. Scripting. Scripts. - Professional Review. 1987 (Box 52)
  - Search for Life. Scripting. Scripts. - Video Service List. 1987 (Box 52)
  - Search for Life.Scripting. Scripts. - Text Addendum. 1987 (Box 52)
  - Search for Life. Scripting. Scripts. - Report with Object Walk-Through. 1987 (Box 52)
  - Search for Life. Scripting. Scripts. - Object Source List. 1987 (Box 52)
  - Search for Life. Scripting. Scripts. - Video Transcript. 1987 (Box 52)
  - Search for Life. Scripting. Scripts. - Exhibition Labels. 2 files. 1987 (Box 52)
  - Search for Life. Scripting. Scripts. - Addendum to Exhibition Labels. Credit. 1987 (Box 52)
  - Search for Life. Scripting. Scripts. - Background. 3 files. 1987 (Box 52)
  - Search for Life. Photos and Visuals. Logo. 1987 (Box 52)
  - Search for Life. Technical Manual. 1987 (Box 53)
  - Search for Life. Aucom Report. 1987 (Box 53)
  - Search for Life. Proposals. Books "State Agriculture Experiment Stations". undated (Box 53)
  - Search for Life. Proposals. US Department Agriculture. undated (Box 53)
  - Search for Life. Exhibit Proposals. Feasibility Study. Schematic Design. 1985 (Box 53)
  - Search for Life. 6 books. undated (Box 53)
  - Search for Life. Photos and Visuals. 1986-1988 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Photos and Visuals. - Visual Rights and Permission. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Photos and Visuals. - Photos. 8x10s. Slides. 3x5s. Negatives. 1986 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Photos and Visuals. - Exhibit Photos. 1988 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Media. 1986-1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Media. - Media Package. Memorandum. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Media. - Environment Package. 1986 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Media. - Sound Package. file empty. 1986 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Media. - Security Package. 1986 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Media. - Lighting Package. 1986 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Media. - Systems Engineering. Codes. 1986 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Media. - Interactive Video. 1986 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Media. - Cartoons. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Media. - Software Rights. Permissions. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Media. - Projection Package. 1986 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Media. - Permissions. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Media. - Wall Graph, Xerox Book of Size and Cropping. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Crick. Watson. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Rosalind Franklin. X-Ray Photo DNA. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Alfred Hershey. Martha Chase. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Robert Halley. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Khorana. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Julie Yindermann. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Max Delbruck. Salvador Luria. Transparency. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Barbara McClintock. Slide. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Bruce Merrifield. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Mendel. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Seveio Ochoa. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Linus Pauling. Early. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Linus Pauling. Late. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Wendell Stanley. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Edward Tatum. 8x10 photo. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Maurice Wilkins. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Asilomar. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Eugenics. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Cal Tech Lab. Gates. Lab. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Rockefeller Institute. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Oswald Avery. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - George Beadle. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Paul Berg. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Herbert Boyer. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Stanley Cohen. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Darwin. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Charles Davenport. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Norman Borlaug. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Bubbles. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Bucolic Farm. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Code Panel. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - DNA Models. Slides. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Front Room. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Arthur Kornberg. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Games. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Mapping the Barley Genome. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Jaques Monod. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Neurospora. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Marshall Nirenberg. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Nobel Prizes. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Hamilton Smith. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Tonegawa. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - David Vetter. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Intro Slides. Storybook Blanks. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Wall Graph. - Future. 1987 (Box 54)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - Storyboards for introducing slide show. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #1 Clockworks. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #2-9 Clock face. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #8-11 Young Darwin. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #11A Origin of Species. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #12-15 Finches. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #15-20 Color. Darwin's Finches. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #21A,B Skeletons. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #22 "Old" Darwin. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #23 Pea Plant Drawings. 2 images. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #24 Teewenhock Pea Drawings. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #25 Mendel Group Portrait. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #28 Mendel Photo Alone. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #29-39 Culinary Pea Diagram. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #41 Tall/Dwarf Pea Cross Diagram. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #42 Wheatfield. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #43 C. Davenport. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #44 CSH Lab. Early Scene. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #45 CSH Lab. Group Early Scene Scientists. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #46 CSH Lab. 1980s. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #47 CSHL. Color Gronads. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #48-49 George Shull. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #49 George Shull. Cover Plot. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #50-52 Corn Field. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #53 Corn. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #56 Exterior. Columbia University. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #57-61,73 Durospohila. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #62 T.H. Morgan. Young. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #63 T.H. Morgan. Old. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #64-66 Teewenhock Fly. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #67-72 Drosophila A. B. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #74-75 Cross White and Red Dros. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #76 "Fly Room" at Columbia. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #77 Gates - Interior and Exterior. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #78 Cal Tech Aerial. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #80 A. Sturtevant 1927. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #81 Bridges, Sturt., Mahr. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #82 Cal Tech Lab with People. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #82A Cal Tech Lab without People. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #83 McClintock. Cap and Gown. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #84-89 McClintock with Corn. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #85 McClintock. Late in Life. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #86-91 McClintock. Nobel. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - #94 Wheatfield. Color. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Intro Slide Show. - Outakes. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - Storyboards. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - Storyboard Blanks. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #1. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #2-5 Universe. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #3-7 Earth in Space. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #8 Sunrise. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #9 Corn. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #10 Corn. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #11 Soybeans. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #12 Soybeans. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #13 Soybean Heap. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #14 Single Soybean Leaf. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #15-23 Electric Microscope Soy Sequence. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #23A-B Snowflake Crystals. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #23C-F Vitamin Crystals. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #24. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #25. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #26 DNA Molecule Computer Generated. Photos and negatives. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #43 - 58 Created Graphics. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #59A Human Chromo. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #59B-61 Mitot. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #62A-C Frog Cell Division. 1987 (Box 55)
  - Search for Life. Cell Theatre. - #62A-E Coli. 1987 (Box 55)